mediamonkey.com 2019-12-30

# MediaMonkey » Privacy

The privacy of MediaMonkey users and visitors to mediamonkey.com is important to us. This notice describes the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use MediaMonkey or visit mediamonkey.com, and how we safeguard your information.

We store the e-mail addresses of those who sign up as members of our Forum, Wiki, eSupport application or Mailing List, for the sole purpose of providing these respective services. We will only communicate with your e-mail address inasmuch as you've agreed to, and you may at any point to halt e-mail-based communication. Note that Forums and Wiki content are available to any visitor to this site. Any information disclosed within a Forum or the Wiki is publicly available and you should therefore exercise caution when posting any personal information.

The store on mediamonkey.com is run by Element 5 and SWReg's transaction processing servers. The store collects personal information for transactional purposes. For a complete explanation of how such personal information is handled see the [Element 5](http://cs.mycommerce.com/privacy-policy/mycommerce/mcus/) and [SWReg](https://usd.swreg.org/privacy.htm) Privacy Policies.

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. This information is used for the purposes of optimizing our site.

Our site uses cookies to store information such as your personal preferences so that the site's services (e.g. the forum or eSupport application) are optimized for you. We may also use third party advertisements on our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons within their ads, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings or via third party tools, however, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

MediaMonkey applications allow you to submit logs to Ventis Media which may contain information about your music collection and/or the conditions that may have triggered a bug. This information is used for the sole purpose of solving the problem associated with the log.

The mediamonkey.com web site and MediaMonkey application may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Ventis Media. Ventis Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We do not sell or trade your personal information and will only divulge such information if compelled to by law.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via [our support page](http://mediamonkey.com/support/).
